# **CAN ARSLAN**



arslancan.coding@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/canarsllann



+905331658275



https://www.datacamp.com/profile/canarslan521

## Summary

I graduated in Business Administration and have hands-on experience as a company owner and manager for over 10 years. I gained deep knowledge of business management, project management, entrepreneurship, leadership, and customer relationship. I have improved problem solving, strategic thinking, leading team skills. Additionally, to be graduated from Information Technologies master program and completed lots of courses with certificates about python, machine learning, data science processes. Thus, having competitive advantage on defining business problems, analyzing data, determining the solution path and developing machine learning models.

## **Experience**



### Manager

**Arslan Limited Company** 

Apr 2010 - Present (12 years 4 months +)

As an owner of a small and medium sized enterprise, I have experienced following works and tasks respectively;

- Quality management
- Operation management
- Marketing
- Accounting



#### **Partner**

Arslan Un Mamulleri

May 2010 - Present (12 years 3 months +)



#### Co-Founder

TAG

May 2012 - Sep 2013 (1 year 5 months)

A small e-commerce company is established and improved by me and my friend as co-founder, after some months, it was failed with lots of experiences about entrepreneurship.

#### **Education**



### MEF University

Master's degree, Information Technology

Lectures included by the program;

- \* Machine Learning
- \* Data Science
- \* OOP with Python
- \* Artificial Intelligence
- \* IOT
- \* Natural Language Processing

- \* Neural Networks
- \* Agile Management and DevOps
- \* Big Data Management

## **MEF University**

Bachelor of Business Administration - BBA, Business Administration and Management, General

Lectures are taken for special self improvement;

- \* Business Strategies
- \* Agile Project Management
- \* Company Valuation
- \* Mergers & Acquisitions
- \* Managerial Accounting
- \* Marketing Strategies
- \* Branding

# Özyeğin University

Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management, General

# Yeşilköy Anatolian High School

High School Diploma

Sep 2006 - Jun 2010

- \* One of the most successful and hard to be a member high school in Turkey
- \* Strong math fundamentals are taken
- \* Strong english fundamentals are taken

# Taş College

Sep 2003 - Jun 2006

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

W Business English: Planning & Negotiating - University of Washington

W Business English: Meetings - University of Washington

**W** Business English: Making Presentations - University of Washington

Branding and Customer Experience - IE Business School

Brand Identity and Strategy - IE Business School

- From Brand to Image: Creating High Impact Campaigns That Tell Brand Stories IE Business School
- Excel Skills for Business: Intermediate I Macquarie University
- Excel Skills for Business: Essentials Macquarie University
- Applied Plotting, Charting & Data Representation in Python University of Michigan
- Applied Social Network Analysis in Python University of Michigan
- Applied Text Mining in Python University of Michigan
- Applied Machine Learning in Python University of Michigan
- Introduction to Data Science in Python University of Michigan
- W Business English: Networking University of Washington
- Using Python to Access Web Data University of Michigan
- Python Data Structures University of Michigan
- **™** Using Databases with Python University of Michigan
- Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) University of Michigan
- Capstone: Retrieving, Processing, and Visualizing Data with Python University of Michigan
- Data Analyst with Python Career Track DataCamp
- Data Scientist with Python Career Track DataCamp
- Python Programmer Career Track DataCamp

#### Skills

Marketing Strategy • Mathematical Statistics • Team Leadership • Teamwork • Mathematics • Statistical Data Analysis • Data Visualization • Team Management • Leadership • Company Valuation